thank you so much for understanding that
uh industry darkness in the last one
month uh ICC is planning to acquire star
health and shelter but this is only
industry
but I did not see any official press
release yet uh I'm able to connect the
dots so other relatives
somewhere around uh
1312 crores uh worth of shares from Star
health insurance
they have sold SAS of star Health 11312
croresis
affiliated with Fidelity Investments
um I don't know I mean I should not
speak randomly in YouTube
news
so now they have done this uh you know
you know they've got around 3.7 percent
of star health so let us see where it is
going thank you so much